[{"id": 2, "question": "The rain had continued for a week and the flood had created a big river which were running by Nancy Brown's farm. As she tried to gather her cows to a higher ground, she slipped and hit her head on a fallen tree trunk. The fall made her unconscious for a moment or two. When she came to, Lizzie, one of her oldest and favorite cows, was licking her face. At that time, the water level on the farm was still rising. Nancy gathered all her strength to get up and began walking slowly with Lizzie. The rain had become much heavier, and the water in the field was now waist high. Nancy's pace got slower and slower because she felt a great pain in her head. Finally, all she could do was to throw her arm around Lizzie's neck and try to hang on. About 20 minutes later, Lizzie managed to pull herself and...\n\nQ: What did the local people do to help those in the flooded area according to the passage?", "options": ["They put up shelter for them in a school.", "They used helicopters to help carry cows.", "They helped farmers gather their cows.", "They set up an organization called Red Cross."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2329, "question": "Teenagers are under a lot of pressure to be thin. They resort to starving, vomiting and eating only diet foods to try and be thin. Television is a big influence on them. They watch shows like Beverly Hills 90210 andMelrose Placeand feel they need to look as thin as the actresses on these shows. Society is brainwashing young people into believing that being thin is important and necessary. Diet commercials are constantly appearing on our television screens telling us that once we lose weight, we will be happy. While you're standing at the grocery store you are surrounded by magazines claiming to have the newest and best diet. Each month another new diet appears claiming to be the diet to end all diets. If diets really worked, then why are there so many of them? The reason a new diet pops up...\n\nQ: According to the author, which of the following statements is NOT true ?", "options": ["Our society is flooded with diet commercials.", "The latest diet is necessarily better than all the previous ones.", "People in North America become crazy over Dieting.", "All diets are useless in fact"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 128, "question": "Three Central Texas men were honored with the Texas Department of Public Safety's Director's Award in a Tuesday morning ceremony for their heroism in saving the victims of a fiery two car accident. The accident occurred on March 25 when a vehicle lost control while traveling on a rain-soaked State Highway 6 near Baylor Camp Road. It ran into an oncoming vehicle, leaving the occupants trapped inside as both vehicles burst into flames. Bonge was the first on the scene and heard children screaming. He broke through a back window and pulled Mallory Smith, 10, and her sister, Megan Smith,9,from the wreckage. The girls' mother, Beckie Smith, was not with them at the time of the wreck, as they were traveling with their baby sitter, Lisa Bow bin. Beckie Smith still remembers the sickening feeling ...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from what Beckie Smith said that   _  .", "options": ["she regarded the accident as a wonder", "she was frightened by the serious accident", "she thought highly of the rescuers", "she called on others to learn from the rescuers"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3175, "question": "Juac has made the leap from being an African refugee to a chess champion in the United States. His job is to share his expertise with students in schools, chess camps and other events. During Sudan's civil war in the mid-1980s, Juac was forced out of the country with 20,000 0ther so -called Lost Boys. He fled to Ethiopia, then to Kenya staying in a refugee camp for eight years, where he learned to play chess. Juac described a dangerous journey in which half the boys didn't survive. To eat, they had to kill wild animals. \"There were animals on the way. It was about a thousand miles and sometimes there was no water. When we were in Ethiopia, we had to cross the river and there a lot drowned.\" Juac arrived in the United States in 2004 and began working as a security guard. Winning a chess tou...\n\nQ: How long did Juac most probably stay in Ethiopia?", "options": ["About six years.", "About eight years.", "About twelve years.", "About sixteen years."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2880, "question": "On the way home from school, Jack always passes a park. His mother said it was dangerous to pass by the park at night, but it is the fastest way home. Today, after finishing soccer practice, Jack was walking toward the park as usual. Suddenly, Jack heard someone calling him, \"Excuse me!\" Jack turned around, and there was an old woman. \"Yes, ma'am.\" Jack answered politely. \"Don't pass by the park tonight.\" Her voice was weak and dry. \"Okay, ma'am,\" said Jack carelessly. The old woman held Jack's hand strongly, and said, \"I mean it!\" Jack felt the hairs on his neck stand up. As soon as the lady let go of his hand, he started to run. This time, he ran so fast that he didn't have time to think where he was going. When he stopped, he realized he was in the middle of the park. He remembered what...\n\nQ: Why does Jack prefer to pass the park?", "options": ["It's the fastest way home.", "It's fun to cross the park.", "He hopes to meet somebody there.", "He'd like to take adventures."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 395, "question": "There's a man in the habit of hitting me on the head with an umbrella.At first I couldn't stand it;now I'm used to it. I don't know his name.I know he's average in appearance,wears a gray suit.and has a common face one hot morning,when 1 was sitting off a tree-shaded bench in Palermo Park,reading the paper,suddenly I felt something touch my head.It was the very same man who now,as I'm writing.keeps striking me with an umbrella. On that occasion I turned around filled with anger.He just kept on hitting me.I asked him if he was crazy.He didn't even seem to hear me.Thell I threatened to call a policeman.Calmly.cool as a cucumber,he stuck with his task.After a few moments of hesitation,and seeing that he was not about to change his attitude,I stood up and hit him on the nose.The man fell down....\n\nQ: It can be learned from the passage that the man_.", "options": ["shouted loudly while hitting the author", "wanted to tell the author something", "rail after the author breathlessly", "acted as if he were a fly"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 537, "question": "It was 11 pm. Donald Lubeck was lying in bed. Outside, lightning lit up the sky, and thunder shook the house. Suddenly he heard the smoke alarm sounding. Lubeck walked down to see what happened; he opened the door to the kitchen, and flames just went out. The sudden strong wind from the doorway immediately created a large fire from a small one, probably caused by lightning. Lubeck went back to his bedroom to call 911. \"I felt safe because the room had a separate stairway,\" he explains. The phone didn't work, and when Lubeck tried to go down the stairway, he was stopped by a wall of flames. Lubeck realized he was in trouble. His daughter and granddaughters, who lived with him, were away for the night. Up a hill lived Lubeck's neighbors, Jeremie Wentworth and his wife. From his house, Wentwo...\n\nQ: Why did Lubeck feel safe at the beginning?", "options": ["Because he knew how to fight fire.", "Because he thought it was a small fire.", "Because he thought he could get out easily.", "Because he knew his neighbor would help him."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1959, "question": "In today's throw away society, dealing with the city's growing mountain of waste is an inereasing challenge for the city countil . Recently. Edinburgh is faced with the problem of dssposing of about250,000 Million tons of waster a year . Despite different ways to dispose of much of it in a green manner---largely through encouraging tecycling---its aging facilities such as the Powderhall landfill do not have the ability to deal with it. The European Union(EU) has issued a new policy, regulating how such mountains of waster are to hr disposed of. The five councils (Edinburgh. East Lothian. West Lothian. Midlethian and Borders) face fine around $18million a year from 2013 it they don't inerease recycling levels and rely less on landfill. With this in mind, the coumlls got together with the id...\n\nQ: What is the final dream an Edinburgh and Midlothian Country?", "options": ["To open a new landfill nearby", "To close the powder hall landfill in 2015", "To set up a plan for burning waste", "To persuade people to deduce their waste."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 963, "question": "Every fall, many Jewish people around the world celebrate the holiday of Sukkot . They build huts in their backyards, and if it is warm and dry outside, they live in those huts for seven days and nights. Living in a sukkah is meant to remind Jewish people that for 40 years their ancestors lived in huts in the desert. In modern times, it has also become a reminder that many people do not have a place to call home. In 2010, an American reporter named Hoshua Foer was building his own sukkah when he came up with an idea. He wondered what it would be like to have a competition for people around the world to use their imaginations to create modern sukkahs. It would be a design competition. But the sukkah would have to be built according to Jewish laws. These laws are found in an ancient book cal...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE about the first competition?", "options": ["More than 600 sukkahs were built in a park in New York City.", "The winning sukkahs were sold to help homeless people.", "Only American people took part in the competition.", "There were 12 judges voting for the winners."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3402, "question": "One of the best-known American writers of children's books is Alfred Strong, or Doctor Strong, as he is better known to readers everywhere. Now, an art show called \"Doctor Strong From Then to Now\" is travelling around the United States. The pictures and drawings show the history of Doctor Strong. Doctor Strong first became famous almost fifty years ago when his first children's book was published. Since then, he has written forty-five books that have sold more than one hundred million copies around the world. Doctor Strong's books are known for their easy use of words and colorful, hand-drawn pictures. These drawings bring life to his imaginary creatures. The Cat in the Hat, Horton the Elephant, The Grinch Who Stole Christmas, and hundreds of others. The San Diego Museum, in California, or...\n\nQ: Doctor Strong's books are very popular in America because   _  .", "options": ["they are stories about animals such as cats, elephants and so on", "they are written in easy words with colourful pictures", "he organized the art show in California", "they are written in a funny way"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3410, "question": "Friendly doctors are\"bad for their patients'health\",researchers have warned as a new study revealed two thirds of young doctors struggle to be truthful with patients they like. Blurring(...)the lines between social and professional relationships can affect the level of care offered and prevent patients from being honest about important side effects. \"Doctors should avoid adding patients as friends on Facebook,they should not hug or allow patients to call them by their first names\".regulators have warned.\"Those who break the boundaries will face some punishment.\" It comes as a survey of 338 oncologists under the age of 40,found 59 per cent said they found it difficult to tell the truth to those patients they liked.Sixty per cent of respondents said if doctors felt too close to their patient...\n\nQ: Which opinion will Lesley Fallowfield agree with?", "options": ["Oncology is a rewarding profession without challenges.", "The Internet makes it easier for young doctors to break the boundaries.", "It's not the duty of doctors to deal with patients'anxiety.", "Becoming friends with patients will help them recover soon."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3089, "question": "In terms of history, Australian cuisine was on the basis of traditional British cooking brought to the country by the first settlers.Modern Australian cuisine,however.has been heavily influenced by Australia' s Asian and Southeast Asian neighbors.The trend,encouraged by long-term government health programs,is towards low-fat healthy cookery including low-fat meat and lightly cooked,colorful,steamed or fried vegetables.Besides,1ike many English families,in many Australian homes,a widespread tradition of having roast turkey,chicken,and ham for Christmas 1unch or dinner still remains. Generally breakfast is light in most parts of Australia.but in the colder regions porridge or meals similar to the full English breakfast may be consumed.In recent years,however,most Australian people prefer lig...\n\nQ: From the passage, we learn that  _  .", "options": ["fewer and fewer immigrants enter Australia every year", "Subway is a chain restaurant and it is from the USA", "home cooking is becoming more and more popular in Australia", "a typical restaurant mainly offers porridge and noodles for supper"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2545, "question": "The historic center of Vienna has been added to UNESCO's World Cultural Heritage list. Thus, St. Stephen's Cathedral, the Imperial Palace and many other historic buildings are now recognized as being among the 700 outstanding cultural and natural monuments of mankind - others include the Pyramid Fields from Giza to Dahshur, the historic center of Rome, the Kremlin with the Red Square, the Chinese Wall, the Taj Mahal and the Grand Canyon. Vienna's historic center, in its unity, is considered one of the most beautiful city landmarks in Europe. Three eras left their mark on the former residence of the Habsburgs: the Middle Ages with Gothic St. Stephen's Cathedral whose spire points toward heaven, one of Vienna's landmarks; the Baroque whose most important achievement is the Imperial Palace wi...\n\nQ: Which of the following is not mentioned as cultural and natural monuments ofman-kind?", "options": ["the Taj Mahal", "the Pyramid Fields", "the Kremlin with the Red Square", "the Court Chapel"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1816, "question": "I want to tell you a story that changed my life many years ago. We were living in College Station, Texas and my wife and I were on our way home from Houston, Texas one Saturday morning. We decided to stop at a local restaurant to get something to eat since we had enough time. When we finished, we got back into our car and before I started it, we noticed a homeless man standing in front of the building. His clothes were worn and it looked as though he didn't have any money. It was cold and I was sure he wanted something warm to drink; however, it was not this that I remember, because that is not what \"moved\" me. A dog was also walking up to the front of the building. Being a dog owner, I knew that the dog was a mother, and that she had just had some pups . She was hungry and weak and I felt...\n\nQ: What do we know about the dog?", "options": ["The author wanted to help the dog, but he was un-able to.", "The dog and her pups were in danger of dying from hunger.", "The dog was not cute enough to be loved.", "The author didn't like dogs."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1487, "question": "\"No man is an island\" is a well-known line from John Donne's Devotion. It was written more than three hundred years ago. Even now people still agree with him. No one can live a completely lonely life. Without other people, life will become empty and sad. We all need to have friends. For some of us, although making friends is not difficult, feeling shy, we may not want to make the first move. It is also difficult at times to keep the friends we already have. There are many books about friendship, but Dale Carnegie's How to Win Friends and Influence People, written in 1936, is the most famous. This \"how to\" book about getting along with other people became a best seller. It was later put into 28 languages. Dale Carnegie's advice seems to be simple, but can his advice help you? Do you need to...\n\nQ: Which of the following is not talked about in Carnegie's book?", "options": ["Say \"Excuse me\" before you ask.", "Don't visit your neighbors too often.", "Think more about others.", "People enjoy hearing their own names."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3339, "question": "(Reuters)The Thunderbird is one of the most readily recognized creatures of American Indian mythology.While the vast majority of biologists believe the Thunderbird myth to be nothing more than a spiritual symbol, some zoologists believe that the hard may actually exist. I still vividly recall seeing an impossibly large raptor when I was five years old, which a few people have said might be the Thunderbird.Standing in my grandmother's back yard in Alabama, I recall watching an enormous black bird with a swallow - like tail flying directly over me from an oak tree. Its wingspan seemed to be at least three times my height, which would have made it at least fourteen feet across. While the early childhood memory is often unreliable, I clearly remember the details of the \"Thunderbird\".To this ve...\n\nQ: What's the best title for the passage?", "options": ["A massive bird spotted in America", "Could the thunderbird actually exist?", "Some strange birds sighed by people", "Sea eagle, condor, raptor or thunderbird?"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2854, "question": "It was an extremely hot day. My younger brother Walt and I had decided to go swimming in a deep swimming hole across Mr. Blickez's farm and through some woods, because it would be the only way to cool ourselves down. The only problem with our plan was that this farm was guarded by a huge mean Hereford bull . Mr. Blickez had told us that Elsie was the meanest bull in town, maybe even in the county and we believed in him. But the hotter it got, the more we thought there was something _ about what he said. For one thing, we remembered Mr. Blickez liked telling tall tales; for another, Elsie seemed like a strange name for a bull. Finally, I talked Mom into asking permission for us to walk through the farm, and Mr. Blickez agreed. On our way across the farm, we stopped at the fence to admire th...\n\nQ: What's the passage mainly about?", "options": ["The bull guarding Mr.Blickez's farm.", "How friendly the so-called mean bull was.", "The story of visiting the swimming hole.", "How the author changed his attitude to Joanie."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2189, "question": "Recently a committee of the National Academy of Sciences inprefix = st1 /Washingtonreleased a report .It confirmed that world temperatures increased about six-tenths of a degree Celsius in the last one hundred years. The report also confirmed evidence that the level of carbon dioxide in increasing. The best information about climate in the past comes from tests of ice many kilometers deep in Antarctica and Greenland .These tests show that levels of carbon dioxide today are the highest ever measured .These findings have led scientists to believe that carbon dioxide is a major cause of climate warming. Carbon dioxide is released into the atmosphere when fuel is burned. Oil ,coal and wood are all fuels that release the gas .When biological waste breaks down ,it also releases carbon dioxide. H...\n\nQ: The committee report of National Academy of sciences in Washingtonreveals that_.", "options": ["ice from Antarctica and Greenland is appropriate to show the change", "carbon dioxide is released mainly from the fuel", "level of carbon dioxide increases with global temperatures", "carbon dioxide is helpful for tree growth"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 927, "question": "Of course, you know that getting a gift for your dad is a must every Father's Day. Perhaps last year you got him a tie he always wanted, or a watch that had the year of his marriage engraved upon it. Yes, all of those gifts were great, but if this year you'd like to get him a gift that he'll be able to hold onto for a long time without breaking your bank, you should consider making a gift yourself. For example, a keepsake box that holds precious keepsakes can be a simple yet timeless gift. Find a box. It can be a cigar box or hat box, but it really has to be strong and long-lasting. Decorate the inside and outside .of your box with paints, ribbons , fabric and other materials.\" Include some of your personal items that best _ your relationship with your dad or a memory that he and you share...\n\nQ: Making a gift yourself for Father's Day might   _  .", "options": ["show your talent for art", "cost you a lot of money and time", "make your father think about how time flies", "make your father keep the gift for a long time"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2113, "question": "The landmark success of herbal expert Tu Youyou, the first Chinese woman national to win a Nobel prize in science, hasaroused an extreme sense of national pride and hopes on the future of traditional Chinese medicine (TCM). Tu, born in 1930, shared the 2015 Nobel Prize for Physiology or Medicine with Irish-born William Campbell and Japan's Satoshi Omura for her discoveries concerning a therapy against malaria. She discovered Artemisinin , a drug that has significantly reduced thedeath rates for patients suffering from malaria . \"Artemisinin is a gift for the world people from the traditional Chinese medicine. It is of great importance for curing malaria and other infectious diseases and for protecting the health of the world people,\" Tu said in Beijing. \"The discovery of Artemisinin is a s...\n\nQ: How old wasTu You you when she receivedLasker Award?  _", "options": ["85", "81", "45", "25"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 111, "question": "Welcome to Coteborg University Coteborg University is one of Sweden's largest and most popular universities. We are very proud of this and believe that there are several reasons for our popularity. The principal reasons we believe to be the high quality of our education and research and the broad range of courses that we offer. In addition to this, Coteborg University provides an attractive and exceptionally high-standard study environment. Most parts of the university are situated in the city centre and this enriches city life as well as student life. Coteborg has a lot to offer its students: it has a rich and varied cultural life with many theatres, concerts and festivals. For those looking for outdoor life, forests and vast recreation areas are not far away from the city centre; the sea...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is true?", "options": ["The university is in the city centre.", "The students can live outdoor.", "The cultural life of the university is very rich.", "The University has no interest in growing demands of society."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 809, "question": "If you like bicycling as much as you like playing ball and can't seem to decide between the two sports, you may want to consider cycle ball--a fun sport that adopts the key attributes from both activities and transforms it into a totally new game.. Also known as red ball, the game was invented in 1893 by German laborers who wished to play polo , but could not afford horses. While the sport has not _ in North America, it is very fashionable in Europe and even Japan. Played in an indoor court, cycle ball is similar to soccer in many ways--the aim is to score as many goals as possible, and only the goalkeeper is allowed to touch the ball. The one big difference? Use of legs is forbidden. Instead, players have to guide the ball across the court, using the front wheels of their bicycles or with...\n\nQ: What can we know about cycle ball?", "options": ["It is a fast-paced game played in an indoor court", "It was invented in 1893 by poor British people.", "It is another name of soccer played by many people.", "It is a strange game played with normal bikes."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 239, "question": "Discover Artistic Talents across the Country Redtory, Guangzhou Redtory, established in 2009, is a spacious art district often referred to as Guangzhou's 798. Made up of more than 30 old halls, mostly buildings of red brick, the place was originally built in 1956 as Chinese largest can factory. Some of the rusty machines from the old factory have been kept as art equipment, giving the zone an old charm. Where: No. 128 Yuancun Siheng Road, Tianhe District, Guangzhou Opening hours: Mon-Sun 10:30 am-9 pm Tank Loft, Chongqing This 12,000-square-meter art center was established on the site of a used military tank warehouse . It is the largest contemporary art base in western China, featuring modern exhibition, galleries, design studios and art bookstores. The art zone is located on the campus o...\n\nQ: If you are going to visit an art zone at 7pm, which one can you go to?", "options": ["Redtory, Guangzhou.", "Tank Loft, Chongqing.", "M50, Shanghai.", "798 Art Zone, Beijing."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1830, "question": "Being young is great. Most of the parts of your body still work great, you have a full head of hair, you're energetic, and you have a world of opportunity in front of you. However, there's going to come a time when you start to get older. And as you get older, you'll have new responsibilities, complete independence, and perhaps most importantly, less time to recover from mistakes. You see, we all make mistakes in life. Maybe you spent more money than you should have on a car, you passed up on a great job opportunity, or you didn't try as hard as you could have in school. It's a part of life and we learn from it. But there are certain mistakes that are much better made while you're still young and have plenty of time to recover. I'm definitely not telling you that you should purposely go ou...\n\nQ: The following are all the advantages of being young EXCEPT   _  .", "options": ["you have more time to recover from mistakes", "most of the parts of your body still work great", "you have many responsibilities and complete independence", "you have a world of opportunity in front of you"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 803, "question": "Studies show that you may be lied to every day anywhere from 10 to 200 times. We say, \"Nice song.\" \"Honey, you don't look fat in that, no.\" But another study showed that strangers lied three times within the first 10 minutes of meeting each other. We lie more to strangers than we lie to coworkers. Men lie eight times more about themselves than they do other people. Women lie more to protect other people. If you're married, you're going to lie to your wife/ husband in one out of every 10 communications. If you're unmarried, that number drops to three. But look, if at some point you got lied to, it's because you agreed to get lied to. Truth about lying: lying's a cooperative act. Not all lies are harmful. Sometimes we're willing to lie for the sake of social dignity , maybe to keep a private...\n\nQ: According to the passage, a lie works when   _  .", "options": ["the liar's words are sweet enough", "it is given to a complete stranger", "someone gives the liar cooperation", "we are willing to lie for the dignity"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3274, "question": "Europe is now the biggest market for organic food in the world, having grown by 25 percent a year over the past 10 years. Denmark's agriculture minister is herself an organic farmer. The UK market for organic food grew by 55 percent in 2000, while the food market as a whole grew by only one percent. Yet only seven percent of British shoppers account for nearly 60 percent of organic sales. However popular the idea of organic farming may be, it is still an interest for only a few people. So what makes the idea of organic farming popular? Organic farming means farming with natural materials, rather than with man-made fertilizers or pesticides . Organic farmers rely on many methods -- such as crop rotation and the use of resistant varieties, because they are necessary for organic farmers to _ ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE, according to the passage?", "options": ["The UK's agriculture minister is an organic farmer.", "Organic farming is popular with young people.", "Farmers try every means to improve the organic sales system.", "Ninety-three percent of British shoppers don't buy organic products."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1937, "question": "My sister Grace Halloran spent most of her teen years in and out of the juvenile institutions for minor offenses but, at 18 she was sent to prison for stealing a car. After three years behind the bars, she was released. Only a few years later, she was given a sentence far worse--she had an incurable and progressive disorder and would be totally blind. Meanwhile, Grace was also happily pregnant but terrified she would never see her child's face. She believed she would succeed as a mother, although \"success\" had never been in her vocabulary before. She managed well despite fading vision. For years she kept consulting specialists about her eye problems, only to be told that her son would also be blind by the time he was a teenager. She swore to find something, anything, to prevent him from fa...\n\nQ: How did Grace regain her eyesight?", "options": ["By following the treatment from specialists.", "By just trying what was taught in the local college.", "By practicing the principles sought by herself.", "By adopting the experience from other patients."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1583, "question": "Zoe, Damacela, 19, didn't have nice clothes when she was young. It wasn't easy for Zoe's hard-working single mother to make ends meet. They moved in and out of homeless shelters. Everything changed for Zoe in grade nine. At that time, she heard about a sewing class at her school. She signed up and couldn't wait to turn her designs into clothes. The color of the first dress she made was white-black strips. Soon the clothes she wore were all made by her. Other girls at school loved her designs too. They asked her if they could buy dresses from her. Zoe sold her first dress for $13. Unfortunately, it cost her $25 to make the dress. \"I had the creativity in designs,\" says Zoe. \"But I really had no idea about business.\" Zoe kept selling the clothes she designed. Her business was booming, and ev...\n\nQ: After winning the contest, Zoe   _", "options": ["considered it a reward", "expected to be known", "was proud of her own gift", "could hardly believe it"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1328, "question": "City farms are gaining popularity in cities and towns around the United States. City Farms in Edmonston, Maryland, is located near shopping centers, car repair shops and homes. The neighborhood is a working-class community. People do not have very much money, and they have limited access to fresh food in markets. Over the past two years, the farm has attracted volunteers from the community like Marcy Clark. She schools her four children at home. On a recent day she brought them to Eco City Farms for a lesson. Alston Clark thinks his experience very valuable. \"I like coming out here, \"he says, \"You know, you connect with the earth, where your food comes from. You appreciate the food a little bit more. \" Margaret Morgan-Hubbard started Eco City Farms. She thinks of it as a place where people...\n\nQ: In which column of a newspaper can you most probably read this article?", "options": ["People.", "Environment.", "Travel.", "Health."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1277, "question": "In 1974, after filling out fifty applications, going through four interviews, and winning one offer, I took what I could get ----- a teaching job at what I considered a distant wild area: western New Jersey. My characteristic optimism was alive only when I reminded myself that I would be doing what I had wanted to do since I was fourteen ------- teaching English. School started, but I felt more and more as if I were in a foreign country. Was this rural area really New Jersey? My students took a week off when hunting season began. I was told they were also frequently absent in late October to help their fathers make hay on the farms. I was a young woman from New York City, who thought that \"Make hay while the sun shines\" just meant to have a good time. But, still, I was teaching English. I ...\n\nQ: What is the writer's biggest worry after her taskmaster's observation of her class?", "options": ["She couldn't ignore her students' bad behavior any more.", "She migh t lose her students' respect.", "She couldn't teach the same class any more.", "She might lose her teaching job."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1296, "question": "Nervous suspects locked up in Britain's newest police station may feel relieved by a pleasant yellow color on the door . If they are close to confessing a crime , the blue on the wall might _ . Gwent Police have abandoned colors such as greys and browns of the 20th-century police cell and have used color psychology to decorate them . Ystrad Mynach station , which recently opened at a cost of PS5 million has four cells with glass doors for prisoners who suffer from claustrophobia . Designers have painted the frames yellow , which researchers say is a calming color . Other cells contain a royal blue line because psychologists believe that the color is likely to encourage truthfulness . The station has 31 cells , including 12 with a \"live scan\" system for drunken or disturbed prisoners , whic...\n\nQ: Which of the following helps alert officers if someone stops breathing ?", "options": ["Scanning equipment .", "Royal blue lines .", "Glass doors .", "Yellow frames ."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2014, "question": "The old lady was glad to be back at the block of flats where she lived. Her shopping had tired her and the basket had grown heavier with every step of the way home. In the lift her thoughts were on lunch and a good rest, but when she got out at her own floor, both were forgotten in her sudden discovery that her front door was open. She was thinking that she must tell her daily maid the next morning to lock the door, and then she remembered that she had gone shopping after the maid had left and she knew that she had turned both keys in their locks. She walked slowly into the hall and at once noticed that all the room doors were open, yet following her regular practice she had shut them before going out. Looking into the living room she saw a sight of confusion over by her writing desk. It w...\n\nQ: When she saw the front door was open, the old lady forgot about   _  .", "options": ["her basket and desk", "her keys and lunch", "her lunch and rest", "her maid and child"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 592, "question": "In most of the time, I am devoted to my research in the lab with my friend Dave, who loves traveling very much. To make our life colorful and relax ourselves, in July, my friend and I are taking a camping trip. We will travel for four weeks and will tour the United States and part of Canada. We have decided to camp because it does not cost as much as vacationing in hotels. We have to plan very carefully in advance. First, the car we are going to drive is very small, so we have decided to take only one small suitcase each and as few camping things as possible. We will take some medicine with us to prevent insects from hurting us, and also food for picnics. Second, there is a lot to see in the United States and Canada, so we have to decide on the direction we want to drive. The date we are l...\n\nQ: The two friends are going to take a camping trip   _  .", "options": ["if they have four weeks' time off", "though it will be a long trip", "so that they can save money", "because it will be warm enough in July"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1631, "question": "Most people consider skydiving a product of the 20th century, but its history actually goes further back than that. The Chinese attempted to parachute in the 10th century, a thousand years before we did. The Chinese did what we would today call base diving; that is, they jumped off a place that would allow them to float from a height to the ground. The first person to attempt to parachute was a Frenchman named Jacques Garnerin. He jumped from his hot-air balloon at the end of the 18th century and did tricks on the way down and _ the crowds by landing safely on the ground. At the end of the 19th century, Kathie Paulus, a brave German woman, became famous for her skydiving skills. Once the airplane was invented, skydiving took on a whole new form. The airplane made it possible to dive from g...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE?", "options": ["The Chinese attempted different skydiving skills in the 10th century.", "Skydiving became popular after the airplane was invented.", "The word skydiving was first used in a military action.", "There were no skydiving schools until the late 1950s."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2214, "question": "Picking up objects plays an important role in people's life. El-E is a robot that is designed to get everyday objects for people with disabilities. About 1.5 meters tall, with a single robotic arm that can pick up objects at different heights, El-E is equipped to discover what its owner wants and then go and fetch it. The user can point a location to the robot using a \"point-and-click\" way of interaction, which provides a direct way to tell the robot which object to handle or where to go. The robot can adapt the position of its arm in order to grasp the object. After successful early trials, some scientists expanded El-E's functions and tried to combine voice commands with the laser in order to do more complicated tasks, like opening doors. The robot recognizes words such as \"pull\" or \"pus...\n\nQ: What is the purpose of the text?", "options": ["To describe different types of El-E.", "To predict the development of El-E.", "To introduce the functions of El-E.", "To stress the importance of El-E."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 45, "question": "A new law helps people with disabilities. The law says that people with disabilities must be able to get into and out of all public buildings. It also says that business must offer special services to people who have special needs. Companies can not refuse to hire disabled workers. Many businesses may have to change their buildings and services. --Ramps must be built so people can get into buildings. --Movie theatres must have space for people in wheelchairs and seats for their friends to sit near them. --Elevators must have floor number in _ . This law will help millions of people. One woman who has been in a wheelchair for many years said, \"It is like a dream.\"...\n\nQ: According to the passage we can see that_.", "options": ["it will be difficult for the normal persons to get into the public buildings", "the buildings of all the businesses will have to be changed", "Most businesses used to offer special services to people who have special needs", "it was difficult for the disabled workers to find jobs in the past"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2502, "question": "Alaska's Arctic lakes now freeze later and melt earlier in the year than in 1950,leaving them easy to suffer water loss from evaporation and possibly adding to local warming,a new study finds.The winter ice season near Barrow,Alaska,is shorter than in 1950,researchers reported Jan.30 in the journal The Cryosphere. Lake ice is also thinner each winter.The scientists surveyed 402 lakes on the North Slope,where permafrost (permanently frozen ground)and shallow lakes dominate the areA. In 2011,the lake ice was 38 percent thinner than in 1950,and 22 percent fewer lakes froze through to their bottoms. \"When we saw the actual numbers we were shocked at how dramatic the change has been,\"lead study author Cristina Surdu,of the University of Waterloo in Canada,said in a statement.Surdu and her co-au...\n\nQ: How many days was the winter ice season of Arctic 1akes in 2011 shorter than that in 1950?", "options": ["6 days.", "12 days.", "18 days.", "24 days."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1934, "question": "Claressa was getting ready for a fight. She had boxed many times before. But this time, the prizes were higher than ever. If she won this fight, Claressa would win a spot on the US Olympic Women's Boxing Team. The fight was difficult. Claressa was up against a two-time US champion. \"Her whole game plan was to hold me against the ropes so I wouldn't hit her,\"says Claressa. Claressa didn't give up. She won the fight. And that wasn't all. She also won the title of outstanding fighter for the whole tournament! Claressa, now 17, started boxing when she was just 11. She was inspired by her dad. He had been a fighter when he was younger. But when she first told her dad that she wanted to box, he didn't support her. \"He told me, 'No! No! Boxing is a man's sport,'\" Claressa remembers. \"It made me s...\n\nQ: Which of the following can be inferred from the passage?", "options": ["Claressa was sure to be like a boy in character.", "Claressa had some trouble persuading her father.", "Claressa's father did well in boxing competitions.", "Claressa's father loved her and was afraid to hurt her."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 80, "question": "The best selling children's book, Pipilu Sending You 100 Lives, has been adapted into a homonymous play that will be put on for the first time next March and tour around 50 cities in China. The book was adapted by the Hangzhou based Star Dream Factory. \"We don't want to descend to the average children's dramas that are overly eager to please the kids,\" said Huang Qin, director of Star Dream Factory. \"We want to provide something practically useful and mystically entertaining.\" The original book by Chinese children's book writer Zheng Yuanjie focuses on safety tips for kids. With Zheng's usual _ and simplicity, the book avoids sugar-coating reality. Instead, it illustrates the potential dangers in everyday life and provides possible solutions. Zheng recalled that when he saw his new-born ba...\n\nQ: Pipilu Sending You 100 Lives has been adapted into a play by   _  .", "options": ["Huang Qin .", "Zheng Yuanjie.", "Guo Yan.", "Star Dream Factory"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3122, "question": "As part of an effort to improve treatments for life-threatening illnesses, a team of scientists have created rabbits that glow in the dark. The efforts have produced two rabbits out of a litter of eight that went from being a normal, soft white to glowing green in the dark. The rabbits were born at the University of Istanbul as part of the cooperation between scientists from universities in Turkey and Hawaii. The rabbits glow to show that a genetic operation technique can work efficiently. \"The green is not important at all--it's just a marker to show the experiment can be done successfully,\" said University of Hawaii associate professor, Stefan Moisyadi. To produce the glowing effect, researchers injected jellyfish DNA into a mother rabbit's embryos. Then those embryos were put into the m...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE, according to the passage?", "options": ["The success rate in creating the rabbits is 20%.", "The project is supported by people.", "The project has been conducted for about eight years.", "The project is mainly conducted by Turkish scientists."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2878, "question": "A 56-year-old Canadian man who left home after his business went bankrupt completed an 11-year walk around the world on Sunday, and told a crowd of well-wishers his new goal was to promote peace. Jean Beliveau -- who arrived to a hero's welcome in Montreal from loved ones, lawmakers and supporters -- said his \"real aim \" was to advise Canada and other governments to build \"ministries of peace.\" \"We are all different, and that is what is beautiful about life on Earth -- our different color1s, different beliefs, different political systems,\" he said. \"Those are all musical notes... we must create harmony from them, create a common tune,\" an emotional Beliveau told the crowd gathering at city hall in the old part of the city. Beliveau left Montreal on the day of his 45th birthday -- August 18...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for this passage?", "options": ["How can exercise kill mental problems?", "What is the best way to escape from pain?", "Beliveau, a world peace promoter and his family.", "Canadian man completes 11-year round-the-world walk."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1366, "question": "Tom appeared on the sidewalk with a bucket of whitewash and a long-handled brush. He stopped by the fence in front of the house where he lived with his aunt Polly. He looked at it, and all joy left him. The fence was long and high. He put the brush into the whitewash and moved it along the top of the fence. He repeated the operation. He felt he could not continue and sat down. He knew that his friends would arrive soon with all kinds of interesting plans for the day. They would walk past him and laugh. They would make jokes about his having to work on a beautiful summer Saturday. The thought burned him like fire. He put his hand into his pockets and took out all that he owned. Perhaps he could find some way to pay someone to do the whitewashing for him. But there was nothing of value in hi...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["Tom was good at whitewashing the fence, so he looked at the result of his work with the eye of an artist.", "Tom was unwilling to whitewash the fence, but he managed to let other boys do it for him", "Tom had a lot of friends who are ready to help others.", "Tom was interested in whitewashing the fence."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2800, "question": "Any mistake made in the printing of a stamp raises its value to stamp collectors. A mistake on one inexpensive postage stamp has made the stamp worth a million and a half times its original value. The mistake was made more than a hundred years ago in the British colony of Mauritius, a small island in the Indian Ocean. In 1847 an order for stamps was sent to a London printer-Mauritius was to become the fourth country in the world to issue stamps. Before the order was filled and delivered, a ball was planned at Mauritius' Government House, and stamps were needed to send out the invitations. A local printer was instructed to copy the design for the stamps. He accidentally inscribed the words \"Post Office\" instead of \"Post Paid\" on the several hundred stamps that he printed. Today there are on...\n\nQ: The mistake on the stamps was made   _  .", "options": ["in Mauritius", "at Mauritius Government House", "in a post office", "in London"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2009, "question": "Are you addicted to computer games? Do you stay up all night playing them? Do you feel happy after you play computer games? There's no doubt that the excitement and appealing of games these days makes them hard to put down. We are attracted by the choice when it comes to gaming: You can role play--creating your own fantasy characters and stories, giving you a chance to step out of everyday life into an imaginary world. And there are shooting games where you can let out your anger and depression in violent situations where you kill people with guns. You can get excited from the games. However, can these kinds of games really be fun and can being absorbed in virtual reality be good for us? Should we worry about their effects on our health? Popular games like Grand Theft Auto have been blamed...\n\nQ: The writer used a lot of questions at the beginning to   _  .", "options": ["show his worries about the effect on health", "lead into the topic of the passage", "ask the reader for their own opinions about games", "doubt the advantage of playing computer games"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2178, "question": "The modern Olympic Games, founded in 1896, began as contests between individuals, rather than among nations, with the hope of promoting world peace through sportsmanship. In the beginning, the games were open only to amateurs. An amateur is a person whose involvement in an activity---from sports to science or the arts---is purely for pleasure. Amateurs, whatever their contributions to a field, expect to receive no form of compensation ; professionals, in contrast, perform their work in order to earn a living. From the perspective of many athletes, however, the Olympic playing field has been far from level. Restricting the Olympics to amateurs has precluded the participation of many who could not afford to be unpaid. Countries have always desired to send their best athletes, not their wealt...\n\nQ: The financial support given to athletes by the Soviet government can best be compared to   _  .", "options": ["a gift received on a special occasion, such as a birthday", "money received from a winning lottery ticket", "an allowance paid to a child", "money from charity organization"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2995, "question": "Almost 70 percent of Chinese middle school students have serious problems with their parents, the Beijing Morning Post quoted a survey as saying. The survey showed 6.62 percent of the surveyed students are afraid of their parents while 13.13 percent of them dislike their parents and 56.28 percent were extremely disgusted with or even hate their parents. Only 4.75 percent of the young people surveyed said they like their parents. The recently conducted survey among 3,000 middle school students in a Beijing district asked questions about their attitude toward their parents and family education, the paper said. For many families, conflict between parents and children center on the student's school grades, their weight and their friends. The survey showed that parental influence over children ...\n\nQ: As is indicated in the passage,   _   .", "options": ["Most parents require their children to be the top ones in the class.", "More and more parents have old fashioned ideas.", "More and more families got divorced due to the high education expectations.", "Most parents hope their children will attend Harvard in the future."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 477, "question": "Friends play an important role in our lives, and although we can't be more familiar with the fact of friendship, we often don't clearly understand how we make friends, especially with Americans. Here are some pieces of advice on making friends with Americans: 1. Visiting places Americans enjoy: parties, churches, restaurants, parks and sports clubs. 2. Be willing to take the first step. Don't wait for them to get close to you. Americans in China may not know you speak English. They may be uncomfortable if they can't speak your language. 3. Use small talks to open the conversation. Ask them where they're from, why they come to China, etc. . Remember: Be careful not to ask personal questions about age, salary and so on. 4. Show an interest in their culture, their country or their job. Americ...\n\nQ: According to the text, Americans like to visit the following places except  _  .", "options": ["shopping centers", "parks", "sports clubs", "churches"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3172, "question": "My student teaching experience was a wonderful adventure. I had to deal with various discipline and behavior challenges that occurred again and again. The greatest part of it was the relationship I developed with two students. One of the students was named Michael,whom I met when I was working for a kindergarten. Before I became a morning bus assistant, I'd heard that Michael was a challenging student who would always shout, stand up on the bus, make fun of other students, and distract bus driver. So I decided that each morning, when he got on the bus, I'd have Michael sit beside me. At first he didn't like this idea and pouted about it. But soon he settled down, knowing he had no choice. I began to talk to him about little things outside of school life, such as his weekend activities and ...\n\nQ: The writer first made Michael sit beside him in order to  _  .", "options": ["limit his freedom and his behaviour", "listen to him and know his real thoughts", "talk to him to change his bad attitude", "give him attention and teach him to behave well"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 721, "question": "Mattel Inc. is _ 4.4 million Polly Pocket toys with magnets after some of them caused serious injuries to children who swallowed magnets that fell off. Tiny magnets inside the toys may fall off without being noticed by parents and babysitters. The magnets can be swallowed or placed in children's noses or ears. When more than one magnet is swallowed, the magnets can attract each other and cause intestine perforation which can be deadly. The Consumer Product Safety Commission(CPSC)received 170 reports of the small magnets coming out of these recalled toys. There were three reports of serious injuries to children who swallowed more than one magnet. All three suffered intestinal perforations that required operation. A 2-year-old child stayed in hospital for seven days and a 7-year-old child wa...\n\nQ: The main purpose of the passage is  _  .", "options": ["to criticize Mattel Inc. for their bad products", "to inform readers of Polly Pocket toys recall", "to warn readers the danger of swallowing magnets", "to suggest some ways to return Polly Pocket toys"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2965, "question": "Advertisers tend to think big and perhaps this is why they're always getting criticism. Their critics seem to resent(...) them because they have a gift for self-promotion and because they have so much money to throw around. 'It's unjust,' they say, 'that this entirely unproductive industry (if we can call it that) should absorb millions of pounds each year. It only goes to show how much profit the big companies are making. Why don't they stop advertising and reduce the price of their goods? After all, it's the consumer who pays...' The poor old consumer! He'd have to pay a great deal more if advertising didn't create mass markets for products. It is precisely because of the heavy advertising that consumer goods are so cheap. But we get the wrong idea if we think the only purpose of adverti...\n\nQ: Which of the following is Not True?", "options": ["Advertisement makes contribution to our pockets and we may know everything.", "We can buy what we want.", "Good quality products don't need to be advertised.", "Advertisement makes our life colorful."], "answer": 2}]